Guide to the Yale Law School Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Law School records of the dean
1871-1994
RU 846
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
97.25
(81 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, reports, lecture notes, and assorted administrative files documenting the activities and operations of the dean of the Yale Law School.
Yale Law School
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 26-A (YRG 26-A), Central records and records of the dean of the Yale Law School.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Yale Law School, 2001-2008.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Biographical / Historical
Origins of Yale Law School
The origins of Yale Law School trace to the earliest days of the 19th Century when law was learned by clerking as an apprentice in a lawyer's office. The first law schools, including the one that became Yale, developed out of this apprenticeship system and grew up inside law offices.
The future Yale Law School formed in the office of a New Haven, Connecticut, practitioner, Seth Staples. Staples owned an exceptional library (an attraction for students at a time when law books were scarce), and he began training apprentices in the early 1800s.
By the 1810s his law office had a full-fledged law school. Samuel Hitchcock, one of Staples' former students, became a partner at the office and later, the proprietor of the New Haven Law School.
Affiliation with Yale College
The New Haven Law School affiliated gradually with Yale from the mid-1820s to the mid-1840s. Law Students began receiving Yale degrees in 1843. David Daggett, a former U.S. senator from Connecticut, joined Hitchcock as co-proprietor of the school in 1824. In 1826 Yale named Daggett to be professor of law in Yale College, where he lectured to undergraduates on public law and government.
Yale Law School remained fragile for decades. At the death of Samuel Hitchcock in 1845 and again upon the death of his successor, Henry Dutton, in 1869, the University came near to closing the School.
Mission of the School
In the last decades of the 19th Century, Yale began to take the mission of university legal education seriously, and to articulate for Yale Law School two traits that would come to be hallmarks of the School.
First, Yale Law School would be small and humane; it would resist the pressures that were emerging in university law schools elsewhere toward large enrollments and impersonal faculty-student relations. Second, Yale Law School would be interdisciplinary in its approach to teaching the law.
Initially, the Law School achieved its links to other fields of knowledge by selecting members of other departments of the University to teach in the Law School. Across the 20th century, Yale pioneered the appointment to the law faculty of professors ranging from economics to psychiatry. This led Yale Law School away from the preoccupation with private law that then typified American legal education, and toward serious engagement with public and international law.
Revival of the School
The revival of Yale Law School after 1869 was led by its first full-time dean, Francis Wayland, who helped the School establish its philanthropic base. It was during this time that the modern law library was organized. It was also during this period that The Yale Law Journal was started and Yale's pioneering efforts in graduate programs in law began; the degree of Master of Laws was offered for the first time in 1876.
After 1900, Yale Law School acquired its character as a dynamic center of legal scholarship. In the 1930s Yale Law School spawned the movement known as legal realism, which has reshaped the way American lawyers understand the function of legal rules and the work of courts and judges.
The realists directed attention to factors not captured in the rules, ranging from the attitudes of judges and jurors to the nuances of the facts of particular cases. Under the influence of realism, American legal doctrine has become less conceptual and more empirical. Under Dean Charles Clark (1929 -1939), the School built a faculty that included such legendary figures as Thurman Arnold, Edwin Borchard, future U.S. Supreme Court Justice William O. Douglas, Jerome Frank, Underhill Moore, Walton Hamilton, and Wesley Sturges. Clark was the moving figure during these years in crafting the Federal Rules of Civil Procedure, the foundation of modern American procedure.
Emphasis on public law
Yale Law School's tradition of emphasizing public as well as private law proved ever more prescient as events of the 20th century increased the role of public affairs in the life of the law. Yale graduates found themselves uniquely well prepared to play important roles in the rise of the administrative state, the internationalization following the World Wars, and the domestic civil rights movement.
In the 1950s and 1960s, the School became renowned as a center of constitutional law, taxation, commercial law, international law, antitrust, and law and economics. In recent decades the pace of curricular innovation has, if anything, quickened, as the School has developed new strengths in such fields as comparative constitutional law, corporate finance, environmental law, gender studies, international human rights, and legal history, as well as an array of clinical programs taught by a clinical faculty of exceptional breadth and devotion.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, lecture notes, and assorted administrative files documenting the activities and operations of the dean of the Yale Law School.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Deans (Education); Law schools; Law -- Study and teaching; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale Law School; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Curricula
- Records of the dean of the Yale Law School, 1871-1994; Accession 2001-A-040
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2020
  - Dean Harry H. Wellington
    - Correspondence files, 1957-1973
      - A, 1962 - 1964, 1966 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Agendas, Announcements, Applications, Brochure, Memos, Resume (Box 1)
      - B, 1961 - 1964, 1966 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Lists, Memos, Resumes, Travel and Expense Reports (Box 1)
        - Telegram (Box 1)
      - C, 1957, 1960 - 1972, 1981 (Box 1)
        - Bulletin, Draft/Report, Lists, Memos, Proposal (Box 1)
      - D, 1961 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Memo (Box 1)
      - E, 1963 - 1973 (Box 1)
        - Memos (Box 1)
      - F, 1961 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Memos (Box 1)
      - G, 1961 - 1963, 1965 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Applications, Lists, Memos (Box 1)
      - H, 1961 - 1964, 1966 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Announcements, Applications, Memos, Proposal (Box 1)
      - I, 1966 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Memos, Pamphlets, Proposal (Box 1)
      - J, 1966 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Announcements, Draft, Memos, Minutes, Reports (Box 1)
      - K, 1961 - 1964, 1968 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Application, Draft, Memos, Resume (Box 1)
      - L, 1961 - 1963, 1966 -1972 (Box 1)
        - Agenda, Drafts, Memos, Notes, Press Release, Questionnaire, Reports (Box 1)
      - M, 1962 - 1964, 1966 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Bill, Brochure, Map, Memos (Box 1)
      - N, 1962 - 1964, 1966 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Lists, Memos, Press Releases (Box 1)
      - O, 1964, 1966 - 1970 (Box 1)
        - Proposal (Box 1)
      - P, 1961 - 1964, 1966 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Announcement, Drafts, Memos, Press Releases, Reports (Box 1)
      - Q, 1972 (Box 1)
      - R, 1962 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Memos, Resumes (Box 1)
      - S, 1961 - 1973 (Box 1)
        - Applications, Bibliography, Memos, Notes, Photos, Report, Resume (Box 1)
      - T, 1961- 1972 (Box 1)
        - Memos (Box 1)
      - U, 1962, 1966 - 1969 (Box 1)
        - Report, Survey (Box 1)
      - V, 1962- 1970 (Box 1)
      - W, 1962 - 1972 (Box 1)
        - Draft, Memos, Newspaper Clipping, Resume (Box 1)
      - X, undated (Box 1)
      - Y, 1959- 1971 (Box 1)
      - Z, 1964 - 1967 (Box 1)
  - Dean Harry H. Wellington; Assist./Assoc. Dean Henry V. Poor; and Assoc. Dean John C. Roberts
    - Dean Wellington - Misc. Letters, 1955 - 1962 (Box 2)
    - Dean Wellington - Manilla Envelopes 2 (Box 2)
      - Misc. Letters, 1963 - 1964 (Box 2)
      - Misc. Letters, 1964 - 1965 (Box 2)
    - Moody correspondence, 1974 - 1979 (Box 2)
    - Moody Proposition and Later Correspondence, 1963 - 1973 (Box 2)
  - Dean Harry Wellington
    - Subject files (Box 3)
      - Conferences and committees; Yale Students for Racism (Box 3)
      - N. Y. Law School, 1984 - 1985 (Box 3)
        - Brochures/Leaflets/Pamphlets, Bulletin/Booklet, Contract, Gen. Correspondence (Box 3)
      - CPCU, Chartered Property and Casualty Underwriters - Atlanta, 1986 October 1 (Box 3)
        - Research Assistant Summer, 1985 (Box 3)
        - CJR Civil Justice Reform Coalition Continental Ins., 1985 - 1986 (Box 3)
      - Bork Debate: - Ct. of App. For Fed. Circuit, 1987 May (Box 3)
      - Loose Papers (Box 3)
        - Freedom of expression/BAD Bestiality Awareness Days Week, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Envelopes 2 - Wellington (Box 3)
        - Freedom of expression, 1986 (Box 3)
        - The use of Hewitt Quadrangle, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Steelworks v Derecktor - Arbitration, 1985- 1990 (Box 3)
      - Loose Papers (Box 3)
      - Revisiting The People and the Court - Wellington (Box 3)
      - Giamatti Speech - Law School Alumni Lunch, 1985 October 19 (Box 3)
    - ABA American Bar Association insurance: NYC, 1986 September (Box 3)
    - Tom's Wellington Bills - Wolf and Dental, 1986 - 1987 (Box 3)
    - Yale Press - Committee on Publications, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 3)
    - ALI [American Law Institute] Torts, 1985 - 1986 (Box 3)
      - Memos, Notes (Box 3)
    - Elliott Conference, 1985 - 1986 (Box 3)
      - Drafts, Notes (Box 3)
    - Alliance Conference - Phila, 1986 May 19-20 (Box 3)
    - CPR Center for Public Resources, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Misc. Program Information (Box 3)
    - Labor Law Clinical Project, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Loose Papers (Box 3)
      - Senior Appointments Committee - Social Sciences, 1969 (Box 3)
      - Department of Anthropology - Annual Report, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Advis. Comm. Soc. Sci., 1966-1968 (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports, Memos, Minutes, Notes (Box 3)
    - Soc. Sci. Advisory, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports, Drafts, Memos, Minutes (Box 3)
    - Disciplinary - Wellington, 1969 October (Box 3)
      - Memos, Reports (Box 3)
    - Loose Papers, 1969, 1986 - 1987 (Box 3)
      - CPCU - Brochures, Business Cards, Index Note Cards, Misc. Correspondence, Resume (Box 3)
  - Deans Abraham Goldstein, Louis H. Pollak and Henry H. Wellington
  - Law, Science and Medicine (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth Report (Box 3)
  - 1975 - 1976 (Box 4)
  - 1973 - 1974 (Box 4)
  - April 1972 Memo (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Report for 1974 - 75, 1974 - 1975 (Box 4)
  - pre-Commonwealth, 1970 - 1974 (Box 4)
  - Drafts, Memos, Misc. Correspondence, Notes (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Report, 1975 - 1976 (Box 4)
  - Benefits, 1974 - 1977 (Box 4)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth, 1972 - 1977 (Box 4)
  - Memos, Misc. Correspondence, Budget/Expense Information (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Report for 1976 - 77, 1976 - 1977 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Seminar in Law, Science and Medicine, 1973 - 1974 (Box 4)
  - Memos (Box 4)
  - Continuation Grant, 1976 - 1977 (Box 4)
  - Memos, Misc. Correspondence, Notes (Box 4)
  - Yale Law School Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
  - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Yale Legislative Services YLS, 1969-1981 (Box 4)
  - Yale University - Counsel Committee on Yale Law School, 1970 - 1983 (Box 4)
  - Memos, Minutes, Misc. Correspondence, Reports (Box 4)
  - Misc. Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Deans Abraham Goldstein, Eugene V. Rostow and Harry H. Wellington - Subject files
  - Civil Liability Program, 1979- 1983 (Box 5)
  - Annual Report, Drafts, Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Proposals, Questionnaire, Reports, Summary (Box 5)
  - Civil Liability Program, 1977-1983 (Box 5)
  - Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Notes, Proposals (Box 5)
  - Reports, Summaries (Box 5)
  - General Electric, 1967 - 1969 (Box 5)
  - Gen. Correspondence, Memo (Box 5)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1961-1984 (Box 5)
  - Applications, Bibliographies, Biographical Sketches, Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Notes, Resumes (Box 5)
  - Judicial Council of CT., 1970-1985 (Box 5)
  - Agendas, Drafts, Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Minutes, Reports, Rules/Regulations (Box 5)
  - Agenda, Draft, Gen. Correspondence, List (Box 5)
  - Brochures, Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Notes (Box 5)
    - Trip to Florida - Harry Wellington, 1983 February (Box 5)
    - No contents (Box 5)
    - Trip to Florida, H. Wellington, 1982 (Box 5)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Memos, Notes (Box 5)
    - Graduate Committee, 1965-1982 (Box 5)
      - Agendas, Journal Article, Drafts, Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Minutes, Proposals, Reports (Box 5)
    - Hawaii Seminar, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Brochures, Gen. Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Gifts, Miscellaneous, 1965 - 1975 (Box 5)
      - Booklet, Gen./Personal Correspondence, Memos, Photos (Box 5)
  - Deans Abraham Goldstein and Harry H. Wellington - Subject files
    - Faculty Memos, 1983 - 1984 (Box 6)
    - First Term Small Groups, 1970 - 1983 (Box 6)
      - Memos (Box 6)
    - First Year Students, 1969, 1971 - 1975, 1980 (Box 6)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Fees, Tuition for Assorted Students, 1965-1974 (Box 6)
      - Memos (Box 6)
    - Federal Relations, 1981 (Box 6)
      - Memo (Box 6)
    - Federal Work Study Program, 1983 - 1984 (Box 6)
      - Memo (Box 6)
    - Fellowship and Research Grant, 1979 (Box 6)
      - Memos (Box 6)
    - Fellows - Senior, Research, etc., 1968-1975 (Box 6)
    - Faculty Leaves, 1976-1978 (Box 6)
      - Misc. Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Faculty Leaves, 1976-1979 (Box 6)
      - Misc. Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Faculty Leaves, 1979-1980 (Box 6)
      - Memos (Box 6)
    - Faculty Leaves, 1981 - 1983 (Box 6)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Loose Papers, Faculty Leaves, 1980 - 1982 (Box 6)
      - Memos (Box 6)
    - Faculty Leaves, 1980-1985 (Box 6)
      - Memos (Box 6)
    - Faculty Leaves, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
      - Memos (Box 6)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1963-1978 (Box 6)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1970-1980 (Box 6)
    - Deanship Appointment Process, 1964- 1979 (Box 6)
      - Memos, Notes (Box 6)
    - Faculty Research Assistants, Leaves, 1966- 1975 (Box 6)
      - Memos (Box 6)
    - Economic Search Committee, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Financial Aid, 1978 - 1983 (Box 6)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Deanship, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
    - Discrimination, 1965-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Dining Halls, 1965- 1982 (Box 6)
      - Memos (Box 6)
    - Discipline - University Tribunal, 1968- 1975 (Box 6)
      - Memos, Reports (Box 6)
    - Danbury Project - Legal Services Organization, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Deans 6 Meetings, 1978-1985 (Box 6)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Divisional Program Related Papers, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Dixwell Legal Rights Association, 1965-1970 (Box 6)
      - Misc. Correspondence, Proposal (Box 6)
  - Deans Abraham Goldstein and Harry H. Wellington - Committee materials Fellowship and Visiting Lecture, Yale Legislative Services, 1970-1983
    - Visiting Lecturers Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 9)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Sherry Parties, 1970-1983 (Box 9)
      - Memos (Box 9)
    - Student Representatives, 1970-1981 (Box 9)
      - Memos (Box 9)
    - Yale Law School Fund Board,, HHW Deanship, 1975-1982 (Box 9)
      - Misc. Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Student-Funded Fellowships, HH Wellington Deanship, 1970-1979 (Box 9)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Law, Science and Medicine, Commonwealth Fund, 1970-1979 (Box 9)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Yale Law School Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Visiting Lectures Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 9)
      - Memos (Box 9)
    - Yale Legislative Services, 1972-1974 (Box 9)
      - Memos, Reports (Box 9)
    - Yale Legislative Services, 1970-1971, 1983 (Box 9)
      - Memos (Box 9)
  - Deans Abraham Goldstein and Harry H. Wellington - Subject files concerning deanships, courses, and prizes; Correspondence, 1966-1985
    - Adverse Publicity, HHW Deanship, 1980-1981 (Box 10)
      - Gen. Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Association of American Law Schools; information booklets, 1980-1983 (Box 10)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Lists (Box 10)
    - A.A.L.S., Association of American Law Schools, general, 1979-1982 (Box 10)
      - Booklets, Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Notes, Questionnaires (Box 10)
    - Law and Modernization, Harry Wellington Deanship, 1974-1976 (Box 10)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Reports (Box 10)
    - Law and Modernization, A.S. Goldstein Deanship, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Budgets/Financial Reports, Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Proposals (Box 10)
    - Letters of Support for Applicants to Law School,, HHW Deanship, 1980-1984 (Box 10)
      - Resumes (Box 10)
    - PRIZES AWARDED Yale Law Sch., 1968- 1985 (Box 10)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Minutes, Notes (Box 10)
    - Placement - General, Harry Wellington Deanship, 1974-1984 (Box 10)
      - Booklets, Gen. Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, Regulations, Reports (Box 10)
  - Deans Abraham Goldstein and Harry H. Wellington - Annual Reports and Correspondence files, 1963-1985
    - Placement, 1980-1984 (Box 11)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Minutes, Notes, Proposals, Reports (Box 11)
    - Pre-participation Program,, Correspondence, A. Goldstein Deanship, 1969-1970 (Box 11)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Memos, Reports (Box 11)
    - Provost's Office Correspondence, Harry Wellington Deanship, 1975-1985 (Box 11)
      - Memos (Box 11)
    - President's Office, Harry Wellington Deanship, 1963-1965, 1970-1985 (Box 11)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Memos, Minutes (Box 11)
    - Loose Papers - Annual Report of the Dean, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - Annual Report of the Dean of YLS, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
    - Summer Stipends, 1982-1984 (Box 11)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Memos, Proposals (Box 11)
    - Summer Stipends, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Proposals (Box 11)
    - Summer Stipends, 1982-1983 (Box 11)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Proposals (Box 11)
    - Annual Report of the Dean of YLS, 1975-1976 (Box 11)
    - Annual Report of the Dean of Yale Law School, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
    - Dean's Annual Report - Yr., 1977-1978 (Box 11)
    - Dean's Annual Report - Yr., 1978-1979 (Box 11)
    - Dean's Annual Report - Yr., 1979-1980 (Box 11)
    - Loose Papers - Annual Report of the Dean of Yale Law School, 1980-1983 (Box 11)
  - Dean Harry H. Wellington - Correspondence notebooks (9); Dean's Report; Applications For Research Stipends, 1975-1984
    - H.H.W. Masters, 1975-1977 (Box 12)
      - Bibliographies, Lists, Memos, Minutes, Reports, Resumes (Box 12)
    - H.H.W. Masters, 1977-1978 (Box 12)
      - Bibliographies, Lists, Memos, Minutes, Resumes (Box 12)
    - H.H.W. Masters, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
      - Bibliographies, Lists, Memos, Resumes (Box 12)
    - Memorandum Copies, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
      - Bibliographies, Resumes (Box 12)
    - Harry H. Wellington, Dean - Memos, 1981 (Box 12)
      - Bibliographies, Lists, Reports, Resumes (Box 12)
    - Chronological File, Sesquicentennial Campaign Thank You Letters;, Nos. 1 - 278, 1978 - 1980 (Box 12)
    - Dean's Report, 2 copies, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - Applications For Research Stipends - 1981 blue 3-ring binder w/color tabs (Box 12)
  - Dean Harry H. Wellington - Committee files, 1966-1985
    - American Bar Association, 1976-1985 (Box 13)
      - Annual Report, Budget, Gen. Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, Newsletters, Position Paper, Program Manual (Box 13)
    - Adirondack Conservancy, 1978 (Box 13)
      - Gen. Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Wellington Deanship, 1976-1982 (Box 13)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Manual Policies and Procedures, Memos, Newsletters, Program Annual Meeting, Report (Box 13)
    - ABA Deans' Meeting Dallas, 1979 (Box 13)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Lists, Memos, Notes (Box 13)
    - A.B.A. Atlanta, 1983 (Box 13)
      - Memos (Box 13)
    - American Bar Assn. Misc. HH Wellington Deanship, 1976-1982 (Box 13)
      - Annual Report, Memos, Newsletters, Planning Guide and Program Manual Law Day, Proposals, Questionnaires, Standards and Rules of Procedures (Box 13)
    - American Journal of Comparative Law, 1968-1976 (Box 13)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, Roster (Box 13)
    - American Society of International Law, 1972-1976 (Box 13)
      - Gen. Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Dean's Report, Annual Report Mailing List, Etc., Wellington Deanship, 1966- 1984 (Box 13)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Memos (Box 13)
    - Appointment Cte Matters Summer Stuff, 1981-1983 (Box 13)
      - Gen. Correspondence, Memos, Notes, Resumes (Box 13)
    - Clare Committee, 1978 (Box 13)
      - Articles, Reports (Box 13)
  - Deans Abraham Goldstein and Harry H. Wellington - Committee files: Appointments, Bar Admissions and Budget; Supreme Court Clerkships; Commencement files, 1969-1984
    - Supreme Court Clerkships, 1969-1982 (Box 14)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Graduation, 1982 May 24 (Box 14)
      - Memos (Box 14)
    - Commencement, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Commencement, 1983 (Box 14)
      - Memos (Box 14)
    - Commencement Files, 1971- 1984 (Box 14)
      - Memos (Box 14)
    - Bar Admissions Clare Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 14)
      - Misc. Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Bar Admissions Clare Cte., 1975-1976 (Box 14)
      - Misc. Correspondence, Reports (Box 14)
    - Appointments Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Bar Admissions-AALS Association of American Law Schools, 2d Circuit Practice Rule, 1974-1978 (Box 14)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Budget for, 1979- 1984 (Box 14)
      - Memos (Box 14)
    - Catalog, 1970- 1982 (Box 14)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 14)
  - Deans Abraham Goldstein and Harry H. Wellington - Subject files, 1967-1983
    - Alumni Weekend Years, Harry H. Wellington Deanship, 1977-1983 (Box 15)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Benign Neglect File, Harry Wellington Deanship, 1975-1985 (Box 15)
      - Misc. Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Council of Law-Related Studies, Harry Wellington Deanship, 1975-1985 (Box 15)
      - Misc. Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Connecticut Bar Foundation, Faculty Admissions, Harry Wellington Deanship, 1971-1985 (Box 15)
      - Misc. Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Controller's Office, Harry Wellington Deanship, 1972-1985 (Box 15)
      - Questionnaires (Box 15)
    - Commission on Alumni Affairs, Harry Wellington Deanship, 1967-1978 (Box 15)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence (Box 15)
    - LEAA, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, white collar crime,, A Goldstein Deanship, 1976-1979 (Box 15)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, Resumes (Box 15)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Grant LEAA, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration,, A. Goldstein - H. Wellington Deanships, 1971-1980 (Box 15)
      - Memos, Misc. Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, Resumes (Box 15)
    - Hopkins Grammar School, 1977 (Box 15)